<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
	<!--Configuration File for Content Parsing-->
	<!--Note this is INSIDE THE FIRST CONFIG TAG-->
	
	<config
		enable_fullscreen="true"
		css_file="content_style.css"
		tween_duration="0.5"
		drag_speed="2.8"	
		
		item_width="300"
		item_height="150"
		item_corner_radius="0"
		item_x_gap="10"
		item_y_gap="10"
		item_default_bgcolor="#666666"
		item_default_padding="15"
		item_complete_fillup="true"
				
		content_width="540"
		content_height="360"
		content_padding="20"
		content_default_bgcolor="#FFFFFF"
		
		close_button="true"
		previous_button="true"
		next_button="true"		
	>
	</config>
	
	<!--Welcome Home Page-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#0066CC"><![CDATA[<p class="white_text"><span class="title_extra">01</span><span class="title_large"> Home </span><br /><br /><span class="desc_small">Tiny welcome square :)</span></p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Welcome to our homepage!</span>
			<p align="justify">This home use the windows concept at <a href="http://www.flashmo.com" target="_parent">flashmo.com</a>
			<span class="highlight">The Project</span> - The primary goal for this project is to build a beautiful flash project site that has a blog-­esque inspiration and a Tumblr feel by combining flash elements with our individual interest in a way meant to capture attention for possibly whoever stumbles across it. The secondary idea beyond this project</p>
			<span class="subtitle">Primary Objective</span>
			<p align="justify">The short term goal of this project is to have a repository of interest stockpiled for us. This will be an information portal for those interested in art, photography, and just wasting time.</p>
			<span class="subtitle">Second Objective</span>
			<p>The long term goal of this project is to create a lasting impact that will promote our marketability and paint our “company” in a positive light: allowing employers to see what our company is capable, and hire us for it. Our site seeks to showcase new technologies, concepts, urban and anything we find to be of interest.</p>]]>
			</content>
	</item>
	<!--About Us Page-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#115566"><![CDATA[<p class="white_text" align="right"><span class="title_large"> About Us </span>   <span class="title_extra">02</span><br /><br /><span class="desc_small">Two IS majors entertaining an idea</span></p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">CMU IS Jr. Yr majors in 70-637</span>
			<p align="justify">We are toying around with this following a tumblr style of things. Mainly the expression of ideas through images.
			<span class="highlight">Emmanuel Agbanyo aka Eman</span>
			<span class="note">Well..., <a href="https://www.facebook.com/emnanah?sk=info">My facebook</a>, just don't spam my wall.</span>
			
			<span class="highlight">Derin Akintilo aka Derin</span>
			<span class="note">See..., <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Muo91/info" target="_parent">My Facebook</a>, just don't spam my wall.</span>
			</p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Contact Us Page-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#AA6600"><![CDATA[<p class="white_text" align="right"><span class="title_large"> Contact Us </span>   <span class="title_extra">03</span><br /><br /><span class="desc_small">Derin and Eman</span></p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">If you want to say hi...</span>
			<p align="justify">Derin and Eman
			<span class="highlight">Already gave you info (Pay Attention)</span>
			<span class="note">Look in our "about us" page. Eventually in V 2.0 we will stick in a php form for contacting us.</p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--SIte Vision Page-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#228844"><![CDATA[<p class="white_text" align="right"><span class="title_large"> Site Vision </span>   <span class="title_extra">04</span><br /><br /><span class="desc_small">Not tumblr :/ </span></p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Our project mindset</span>
			<p align="justify">The current perception we need to overcome is trying to make the site too “web 2.0” and overly generic. Though these sites look simplistic and great, we feel that they lack some personality. The site viewer will want to be impressed by current and emerging technologies.</span>
			<span class="note">We want our visitor to come away thinking they want to return to our site to see the next cool concept we stumble on, the next cool movie we suggest, and generally the next cool thing we find and decide it needs a place to showcase itself on our project page. They will have seen something that can inspire conversation. </span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Subtle Transition Page-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626"><![CDATA[<p class="white_text" align="right"><span class="title_large"></span><span class="desc_small">...On to movies</span></p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title"></span>
			<p align="justify">Nothing to see here, Move along.</span>
			<span class="note">Not even this</span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Movie Intro Subspace-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/mov_rl_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro movie page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Movie Introduction</span>
			<p align="justify">Looking for a movie series to watch all together? Well this is the idea. Instead of getting movies separately. Maybe you want to watch the Paranormal Activity Series, or the Marvel movies for upcoming Avengers? Click away.</span>
			<span class="note">The ratings are taken from imdb and rotten tomatoes</span></p>]]></content>
	</item>	
	<!--Paranormal Activity 2-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/pa1_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>Paranormal Activity 1.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Paranormal Activity 1 (2010)</span>
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: After moving into a suburban home, a couple becomes increasingly disturbed by a nightly demonic presence. 
			<br />RT: A haunted house makes no secret of the fact it's not pleased with its new tenants in this independent tale of supernatural horror. Katie (Katie Featherson) and Micah (Micah Sloat) are a twentysomething couple who've just moved into a new home in San Diego, CA. Katie has an interest in the paranormal and believes that malevolent spirits have been following her since childhood, though Micah is not so easily convinced. However, after several nights of loud noises and strange happenings, Micah starts to agree with Katie that some sort of ghost may have followed them to the new home. After a paranormal researcher tells the couple he can't help them, Micah decides to take control of the situation and sets up a battery of video cameras so that if a spirit manifests itself, he can capture its behavior on tape. Once the surveillance cameras are in place, Katie and Micah bring in a Ouija board in an effort to talk to the spirits, a move that deeply offends the ghosts. Paranormal Activity was the first feature film from writer and director Oren Peli. ~ Mark Deming, Rovi
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1179904/" target="_parent">IMDB: 6.5</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/paranormal_activity/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 82%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: I rate this a 7.0, One of the few I have watched 4 times an enjoyed each time.</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--Paranormal Activity 2-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/pa2_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>Paranormal Activity 2.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Paranormal Activity 2 (2010)</span>	
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: After experiencing what they think are a series of "break-ins", a family sets up security cameras around their home, only to realize that the events unfolding before them are more sinister than they seem.
			<br />RT: The sequel to the low-budget blockbuster Paranormal Activity takes place a few months before the events of the first film. Katie (Katie Featherston), the much put-upon leading lady in the original, has a sister living in an upscale Los Angeles suburb named Kristi (Sprague Grayden). Kristi has a new baby son, Hunter; a likable lug of a husband named Daniel (Brian Boland), who owns several fast-food joints; a teenage stepdaughter from her hubby's first marriage, Ali (Molly Ephraim); and a large, friendly dog. As the family gets used to the new arrival, strange noises are heard late at night and when they come home from an outing, they discover the house has been trashed, even though none of their valuables have been stolen. Daniel responds by installing a security system and a network of surveillance cameras, though that doesn't stop the noises or the Latino housekeeper's insistence that spirits lurk in the home. When Katie and her boyfriend, Micah (Micah Sloat), stop by for a visit, they discuss the strange goings-on with Kristi; the women of the house believe supernatural forces are at work, while the men find that notion ridiculous. That doesn't last long, as the spirits get noisier and angrier, especially when Ali begins doing some research on the subject, and before long the safety of the household is being threatened on several fronts, possibly due to some dirty dealings in the family's distant past. ~ Perry Seibert, Rovi
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1536044/" target="_parent">IMDB: 5.8</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/paranormal_activity_2/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 59%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: I rate this at a 5.0 It confused me so I only watched it once. Some good parts though.</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--Paranormal Activity 3-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/pa3_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>Paranormal Activity 3.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Paranormal Activity 3 (2011)</span>
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: In 1988, young sisters Katie and Kristi befriend an invisible entity who resides in their home.
			<br />RT: The Paranormal Activity franchise continues with this third outing from Paramount Pictures. Oren Peli and Jason Blum return to produce the highly secretive feature, with Catfish's directing duo of Henry Joost and Ariel Schulman taking on the helming duties. ~ Jeremy Wheeler, Rovi
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1778304/" target="_parent">IMDB: 6.1</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/paranormal_activity_3/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 54%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: I rate this at a 6.0 I would rewatch it, some good parts</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--Iron Man 1-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/im1_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>Iron Man Movie Logo For the net.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Iron Man (2008)</span>
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: When wealthy industrialist Tony Stark is forced to build an armored suit after a life-threatening incident, he ultimately decides to use its technology to fight against evil.
			<br />RT: From Marvel Studios and Paramount Pictures comes Iron Man, an action-packed take on the tale of wealthy philanthropist Tony Stark (Robert Downey Jr.), who develops an invulnerable robotic suit to fight the throes of evil. In addition to being filthy rich, billionaire industrialist Tony Stark is also a genius inventor. When Stark is kidnapped and forced to build a diabolical weapon, he instead uses his intelligence and ingenuity to construct an indestructible suit of armor and escape his captors. Once free, Stark discovers a deadly conspiracy that could destabilize the entire globe, and dons his powerful new suit on a mission to stop the villains and save the world. Gwyneth Paltrow co-stars as his secretary, Virginia "Pepper" Potts, while Terrence Howard fills the role of Jim "Rhodey" Rhodes, one of Stark's colleagues, whose military background leads him to help in the formation of the suit. Jon Favreau directs, with Marvel movie veterans Avi Arad and Kevin Feige producing. ~ Jeremy Wheeler, Rovi
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0371746/" target="_parent">IMDB: 7.9</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/iron_man/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 94%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: This movie is insanely addictive</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--Iron Man 2-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/im2_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>Iron Man 2 Movie Logo For the net.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Iron Man 2 (2010)</span>
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: Because of his superhero alter ego, Tony Stark must contend with deadly issues involving the government, his own friends and new enemies.
			<br />RT: As Tony Stark (Robert Downey Jr.) owns up to being Iron Man before the world press, Anton Vanko lies dying in Russia. Years ago, Anton worked with Tony's father to create a new source of energy. But greed got the best of Anton, and now as he slips away, his son, Ivan (Mickey Rourke), vows to make Tony pay for the sins of his father. Meanwhile, Tony fends off efforts from smarmy Senator Stern (Garry Shandling) and military weapons expert Justin Hammer (Sam Rockwell) to get him to divulge the secrets of his powerful Iron Man suit. The powers that be are concerned that Tony's technology may fall into the wrong hands -- fears that are soon confirmed when the cocky billionaire entrepreneur is confronted in front of the entire world by Ivan, who has built his own weapon using stolen Stark blueprints. Later, as Lt. Rhodes (Don Cheadle) wrestles with the decision to personally deliver Tony's suit to the military, Ivan finds an unlikely ally in the quest to destroy Iron Man; Stark Industries legal consultant Natalie Rushman (Scarlett Johansson) reveals her connection to Nick Fury (Samuel L. Jackson); and Pepper Potts (Gwyneth Paltrow) takes on some new responsibilities. ~ Jason Buchanan, Rovi
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0371746/" target="_parent">IMDB: 7.0</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/iron_man/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 74%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: This movie just as action packed as the first</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--The Incredible Hulk-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/ih1_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>The Incredible Hulk Movie Logo.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">The Incredible Hulk (2008)</span>
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: Dr. Bruce Banner, thanks to a gamma ray experiment gone wrong, transforms into a giant green-skinned hulk whenever his pulse rate gets too high. Meanwhile, a soldier uses the same technology to become an evil version of the original.
			<br />RT: Mild-mannered scientist Bruce Banner has been traveling the globe in search of the antidote that will allow him to break free from his primal alter ego, but both the warmongers who long to exploit him for their own gain and a horrific creature known as The Abomination are determined to stop him from achieving his noble goal in Transporter 2 director Louis Leterrier's take on the classic Marvel Comics superhero tale. For years, Bruce (Edward Norton) has been living in the shadows, pursued by the military and haunted by the rage within. But traveling the world in secrecy isn't easy, and as hard as he tries Bruce can't get Betty Ross (Liv Tyler) off his mind. The daughter of Bruce's nemesis Gen. Thaddeus "Thunderbolt" Ross (William Hurt), Betty represents everything that is beautiful in the world to a man who lives his life on the run. Eventually, Bruce returns to civilization and faces the wrath of The Abomination. While the Hulk may be a formidable force of nature, The Abomination is decidedly more powerful, and determined to destroy Bruce Banner. Created when KGB agent Emil Blonsky (Tim Roth) exposed himself to a higher dose of the same radiation that transformed Bruce into The Hulk, The Abomination is unable to change back into human form and holds Bruce accountable for his frightful condition. With time fast running out for both Bruce and The Hulk, New York City is about to become the ultimate urban battle zone as two of the most powerful creatures ever to walk the earth clash in a massive, no-holds-barred fight to the finish. ~ Jason Buchanan, Rovi
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0800080/" target="_parent">IMDB: 7.0</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/the_incredible_hulk/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 66%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: This movie just as action packed as the first</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--Thor-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/tr1_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>The Thor Movie Logo to fill space.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Thor (2011)</span>
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: The powerful but arrogant warrior Thor is cast out of the fantastic realm of Asgard and sent to live amongst humans on Earth, where he soon becomes one of their finest defenders.
			<br />RT: The epic adventure Thor spans the Marvel Universe from present day Earth to the mystical realm of Asgard. At the center of the story is The Mighty Thor, a powerful but arrogant warrior whose reckless actions reignite an ancient war. As a result, Thor is banished to Earth where he is forced to live among humans. When the most dangerous villain of his world sends its darkest forces to invade Earth, Thor learns what it takes to be a true hero.-- (C) Paramount Pictures
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0800369/" target="_parent">IMDB: 7.0</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/thor/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 77%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: I haven't seen this yet, I will soon</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--Captain America-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/ca1_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>The Captain America Movie Logo to fill space.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Captain America (2011)</span>
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: After being deemed unfit for military service, Steve Rogers volunteers for a top secret research project that turns him into Captain America, a superhero dedicated to defending the USA's ideals.
			<br />RT: Captain America: The First Avenger will focus on the early days of the Marvel Universe when Steve Rogers (Chris Evans) volunteers to participate in an experimental program that turns him into the Super Soldier known as Captain America. As Captain America, Rogers joins forces with Bucky Barnes (Sebastian Stan) and Peggy Carter (Hayley Atwell) to wage war on the evil HYDRA organization, led by the villainous Red Skull (Hugo Weaving.) -- (C) Paramount
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0458339/" target="_parent">IMDB: 6.8</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/captain-america/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 79%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: Seems like Captain America 2 is coming out in 2014</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--The Avenger-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/movies/av1_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>The Captain America Movie Logo to fill space.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Marvel's The Avengers (2012)</span>
			<p align="justify">
			IMDB: Nick Fury of S.H.I.E.L.D. brings together a team of super humans to form The Avengers to help save the Earth from Loki and his army.
			<br />RT: Marvel Studios presents Marvel's The Avengers-the Super Hero team up of a lifetime, featuring iconic Marvel Super Heroes Iron Man, The Incredible Hulk, Thor, Captain America, Hawkeye and Black Widow. When an unexpected enemy emerges that threatens global safety and security, Nick Fury, Director of the international peacekeeping agency known as S.H.I.E.L.D., finds himself in need of a team to pull the world back from the brink of disaster. Spanning the globe, a daring recruitment effort begins. -- (C) Marvel
			
			<span class="highlight"><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0848228/" target="_parent">IMDB: 8.9</a>, <a href="http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/marvels_the_avengers/" target="_parent">Rotten Tomatoes: 96%</a></span>
			
			<span class="note">Eman: Waiting until May 4th for this one</span>
			</p>]]>
		</content>
	</item>
	<!--Subtle Transition Page-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626"><![CDATA[<p class="white_text" align="right"><span class="title_large"></span><span class="desc_small">...On to images</span></p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title"></span>
			<p align="justify">Nothing to see here, Move along.</span>
			<span class="note">Not even this</span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Image Intro Subspace-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/images/img_rl_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro image page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Image Introduction</span>
			<p align="justify">Ever seen awe-inspiring, jaw dropping, mind-sparking image you wanted to share? We have and so we present the great things we have found from the internet. These are images are used under creative commons.</span>
			<span class="note">Pictures were taken from http://www.notcot.org/, https://www.tumblr.com/, www.http://www.flickr.com and such wonderful sites</span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Image Page 1-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/images/rs_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro image page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Racing Stars</span>
			<p align="justify">Eman: This image inspires the mind to explore above us, above the Earth, above the night sky. What does it say to you?
			<span class="highlight">Image From: flickr</span>
			<span class="note"><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/stawarz/2981086612/" target="_parent">image credit: Andrew Stawarz</a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Image Page 2-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/images/gs_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro image page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Grey skies over Matsumoto</span>
			<p align="justify">"Matsumoto Castle (松本城, Matsumoto-jō) stands majestically amid the City of Matsumoto, situated 600 meters above sea level near the center of the Matsumoto Basin, and with a background of the 3,000-meter-high Japan Alps, which extends westerly."
			<span class="highlight">Image From: flickr</span>
			<span class="note"><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/zhzheka/701816373/" target="_parent">image credit: eugeniusD80</a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Image Page 3-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/images/qt_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro image page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Q – 2:53AM</span>
			<p align="justify">Eman: As a New Yorker, I can say...it is never this clean. Or this quiet, even at 2:35am!
			<span class="highlight">Image From: flickr</span>
			<span class="note"><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/darn/539225017/" target="_parent">image credit: darn</a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Image Page 4-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/images/mb_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro image page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Modern Building Image</span>
			<p align="justify">"I took this picture at 22:00h, using my Nikon D90, Sigma 10-20mm lens. NO postprocessing, this is the original JPEG captured by the D90. Pretty awesome, artificial... it seems CG" - torek
			<span class="highlight">Image From: flickr</span>
			<span class="note"><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/torek/2981744796/" target="_parent">image credit: torek</a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Image Page 5-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/images/pi_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro image page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Perhentian Islands</span>
			<p align="justify">Eman: Don't you wish you could wash away your troubles in a remote island somewhere?
			<span class="highlight">Image From: flickr</span>
			<span class="note"><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/nadio/936973323/in/set-72157600945628534/" target="_parent">image credit: nadio</a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Subtle Transition Page-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626"><![CDATA[<p class="white_text" align="right"><span class="title_large"></span><span class="desc_small">...On to technologies</span></p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title"></span>
			<p align="justify">Nothing to see here, Move along.</span>
			<span class="note">Not even this</span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Tech Intro Subspace-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="#262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/techs/tec_rl_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro tech page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Tech Introduction</span>
			<p align="justify">Where are my flying cars?! It is 2012 already and I want my flying cars. On the other had look at all these decently cool gagdets and technology! Ooooo, shiny.</span>
			<span class="note">Eman: Feels like I went on a stumbleupon binge...</span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Tech Page 1-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/techs/sb_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro tech page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title"> Sensu: A true painting experience on your iPad</span>
			<p align="justify">Sensu is two very useful tools in one. A brush and a stylus for capacitive devices like the iPad and iPhone. The rubber stylus is exposed when the brush is closed. This stylus is great for sketching and writing or as a general navigation tool. Grasp Sensu near the nib section and pull it out of the protective cap. You will reveal the capacitive bristles of the artist brush. Insert the rubber stylus into the cap and the cap becomes a handle for your brush.
			<span class="highlight">Image from: Uncrate </span>
			<span class="note">Image credit: <a href="http://www.sensubrush.com/" target="_parent">Sensubrush</a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Tech Page 2-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/techs/lh_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro tech page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title"> Logitech Harmony® Link </span>
			<p align="justify">Logitech Harmony Link is a small device that connects to your home Wi-Fi® network. It turns signals from the Harmony Link app into infrared commands that can control your TV, set-top boxes, music systems and many other home entertainment devices. It even has an IR mini blaster that allows it to send signals through closed cabinet doors
			<span class="highlight">Image from: Uncrate </span>
			<span class="note">Image credit: <a href="http://www.logitech.com/en-us/1225/8439" target="_parent">Logitech</a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Tech Page 3-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/techs/at_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro tech page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">AMG V12 Turntable</span>
			<p align="justify">Your vinyl has never sounded looked so good. The AMG V12 Turntable ($15,000) is the first turntable from Analog Manufaktur Germany, featuring a CNC machined 25mm aluminum plinth, a 16mm axle bearing, a CNC machined aluminum platter with a weighted rim, a Lorenzi 2 pulse, low-speed brushless motor, 33.3, 45, and 78 speeds, a belt drive mechanism, a twelve inch tonearm, and devastatingly handsome looks.
				
			<span class="highlight">Image from: Uncrate </span>
			<span class="note">Image credit: <a href="http://www.amg-turntables.com/" target="_parent"> AMG Viela Turntable</a>.</span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Tech Page 4-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/techs/ip_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro tech page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">Apple Ipad 3</span>
			<p align="justify">It's been less than two years since the iPad first landed, but Apple is ready to make the only tablet worth buying even better. Headlining the list of new features on the iPad 3 ($500-$830) is the drool-worthy Retina display, which densely packs in enough pixels that the human eye is unable to distinguish individual pixels when held at a reading distance — you know, like that iPhone 4 in your pocket. The new iPad and that crazy screen is powered by a high performance A5X chip with quad-core graphics (which is still is smart enough to deliver 10 hour battery life). There's also a slick 5 megapixel iSight camera with 1080p HD video recording capability. And for the first time, you can get built-in support for AT&T's and Verizon's 4G LTE networks. Apple also today introduced the iPhoto app, along with major updates to iMovie and GarageBand, completing its suite of iLife apps for iOS. Like always, the latest iPad is available in black or white. It comes in 16GB, 32GB, and 64GB capacities. It will be available on March 16th.
			<span class="highlight">Image from: Uncrate</span>
			<span class="note"> Image credit: <a href="http://www.apple.com/ipad/" target="_parent"> Apple </a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	<!--Tech Page 5-->
	<item>
		<description bgcolor="262626" padding="0"><![CDATA[<img src="content/techs/sg_300x150.jpg" width="300" height="150" vspace="0" hspace="0" /><p>This is the intro tech page.</p>]]></description>
		<content><![CDATA[<span class="title">02 Samsung Galaxy Beam </span>
			<p align="justify">We've seen projectors built into point-and-shoot cameras, but since those are quickly being replaced by smartphones, it was inevitable we'd see a projector pop up in one of those next. And so we have, with the Samsung Galaxy Beam ($TBA). Although its specs are relatively pedestrian — a 1 GHz dual-core processor, 4-inch 480x800 display, Android 2.3, 8GB of memory, and a 5 megapixel camera — it's the 15 lumen projector built into the top that steals the show, letting you share photos and videos on a projected screen up to 50-inches wide. Try doing that with your iPhone.
			<span class="highlight">Image from: Uncrate</span>
			<span class="note">Image credit: <a href="http://www.samsung.com/us/mobile/cell-phones" target="_parent">Samsung </a></span></p>]]></content>
	</item>
	
	
	<!--This is the END of the CONTENT-->
</items>